http://www.ili.org/terms-and-conditions.html

.
HomeContact Us
jtemplate.ru - free extensions Joomla
ABOUTTRAININGTECHNICAL ASSISTANCEPUBLICATIONSCENTERS OF EXPERTISEGLOBAL AFFILIATESOPPORTUNITIESIFC PROGRAMS
TERMS OF USE
This website (this "Site") is administered by the staff at the International Law Institute "ILI".
ILI makes information available on this Site, subject to the following Terms of Use ("Terms"). By accessing this Site, you agree to these Terms. If you do not agree to all of these Terms, do not use this Site. ILI reserves the right to change these Terms at any time without notice. These Terms represent the entire understanding relating to the use of this Site.
SECURITY NOTICE
For SITE SECURITY purposes and to ensure that this site remains available to all users, ILI uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.
Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this site are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.
GENERAL DISCLAIMER
We strongly recommend that ILI data be acquired directly from this Site and not through other sources that may have changed the information in some way or excluded material crucial to the understanding of that information. While we make every effort to provide accurate and complete information, some information may change between Site updates. Substantive changes may be noted when content is next updated.
WARRANTIES AND DISCLAIMERS
ALL MATERIALS ON THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.
The materials posted on this Site could include technical or other mistakes or inaccuracies. ILI disclaims all warranties and makes no representations regarding the quality, accuracy, completeness or suitability of the materials on this or any other website, and disclaims any duty to keep this information current or accurate. ILI shall have the right, and will work diligently to  remove in timely manner, content that may be in violation of this agreement or any rules posted here. ILI may change any information on this Site or any product or service described on this Site, including functionality or performance thereof, any time without notice.
ILI will not make changes to its Privacy Statement.  ILI will work at all time to keep all visitors information secure at all times.  See Privacy Statement
DISCLAIMER OF ENDORSEMENT
The documents posted on this Site may contain hypertext links or pointers to information created and maintained by other public and private organizations. These links and pointers are provided for visitors' convenience. We do not control or guarantee the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, or completeness of any linked information. Further, the inclusion of links or pointers to websites other than an ILI-managed website is not intended to assign importance to those sites and the information contained therein, nor is it intended to endorse, recommend, or favor any views expressed, or commercial products or services offered on these outside sites, or the organizations sponsoring the sites, by trade name, trademark, manufacture, or otherwise.
Reference in this Site to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the Site's visitor's, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by ILI.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
This Site contains links to other websites that are not hosted by ILI. These websites are not under the control of ILI. ILI is not responsible for their content or the content of any information linked to these websites. Links to other websites are provided as a convenience to our visitors and do not imply any endorsement by ILI of information contained in these websites or the organizations that support them.
DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY
IN NO EVENT WILL ILI BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGE WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION DAMAGES RELATING TO LOST REVENUES OR PROFITS, LOST DATA, WORK STOPPAGE, COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION) RESULTING FROM OR IN ANY WAY RELATED TO THE USE OF ANY MATERIALS POSTED ON OR MADE AVAILABLE AT THIS SITE OR ANY OTHER SITE TO WHICH A LINK IS PROVIDED OR ON WHICH A LINK IS PROVIDED TO THIS SITE, REGARDLESS OF THE LEGAL THEORY ON WHICH SUCH DAMAGES ARE BASED.
Every effort is made to provide accurate and complete information. However, we cannot guarantee that there will be no errors. We make no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this Site and expressly disclaim liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this Site.  ILI will always use its best efforts to ensure the accuracy and timeliness of all information.
With respect to the content of this Site, neither ILI, nor its employees and contractors make any warranty, expressed or implied or statutory, including but not limited to warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, and the warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, with respect to content available from this Site or other Internet resources linked from it. Additionally, ILI does not assume any legal liability for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, product, or process disclosed herein nor freedom from computer virus, and does not represent that use of such information, product, or process would not infringe on privately owned rights.
COPYRIGHT NOTICE
This website and its content is copyright of the International Law Institute © 2010. All Rights Reserved.
Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following:
You may print or download to a local hard disk extracts for your personal and non-commercial use only you may copy the content to individual third parties for their personal use, but only if you acknowledge this Site as the source of the material.
You may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the Site's content, nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.
No photo may be copied or downloaded without the written permission of ILI.
This copyright notice does not pertain to information at websites other than this Site.
COMPUTER FRAUD AND ABUSE ACT
Unauthorized attempts to upload information and/or change information on this Site are strictly prohibited and are subject to prosecution under Title 18 U.S.C., Sections1001 and 1030).
REGISTERING WITH THIS SITE
Visitors may register with this site if they wish to receive periodic publicly available information about ILI.
Please see our privacy policy for information on how we protect any personal information you provide to us.
SITE MANAGEMENT
ILI manages the overall information content, design, and, organization of this Site.
FOR MORE INFORMATION
If you have any questions or comments about the information presented here, please contact ILI at the address or phone or email address listed below.
International Law InstituteILI Website / Privacy1055 Thomas Jefferson St. NWSuite M-100Washington, D.C.  20007  USAPhone: +1.202.247.6006 x 114Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
HomeContact UsSearchSite MapTerms and ConditionsNoticesPrivacy Policy
